Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Two thousand five hundred years ago,
a monster started opening the door
that bridges the human realm
to hell in order to make humans suffer.
But the Buddha appeared before the monster
and pulled out
the Red Eye
and the Black Eye,
which were the source of his power.
However, both eyes
escaped the Buddha's hands
and started to run away from the Buddha.
The Black Eye was caught
by the Buddha soon enough
and was locked inside a sarira casket.
But the Red Eye,
on the other hand, managed to get away
by hiding inside people's bodies
and running away for seven nights.
Then, on the eighth night,
the Red Eye stopped and turned around,
thinking it had come far enough.
But upon realizing that the path
it had been on was actually a bridge
consisting of seven stepping stones
over a narrow, shallow stream,
the Red Eye learned that
it could never escape from the Buddha.
So it faked surrender
and voluntarily got into a sarira casket.
After sealing them
inside the caskets and locking them up
in the vast deserts of the west
and the steep cliffs of the east,
the Buddha said to his nameless disciples,
"You must make sure
they never meet again."
"That is your fate."
OCTOBER 2005
INDIA-PAKISTAN BORDER
I've finally figured out
where the sarira casket is in the desert.
If I manage to find it,
I can prove that the legend
of the Diamond Sutra is actually true.
A relic, which can prove the legend
of the Diamond Sutra, has been discovered.
The Buddhist world
is paying close attention to this.
The radiocarbon-dating results are out.
Professor Kim is suspected
of forging the relic.
They will take legal action against him.
…disagrees with results…
The carbon in the black sarira casket
was synthesized recently…
The sarira casket forgery case
caused quite a stir back in 2005.
Due to Professor Kim's bizarre behavior…
AFTER THE RELIC FORGERY CASE
1ST SUPER BLUE BLOOD MOON IN 35 YRS.
14 YEARS LATER
RED MOON TO BE SEEN TONIGHT
TOTAL LUNAR ECLIPSE
FOR 2 HOURS STARTING AT 1:00 AM
The sarira casket is fake?
And the legend is a lie?
What do you people even know?
You idiots…
I was not wrong.
That's right! I wasn't wrong.
You people are the ones
who got it all wrong!
I'll prove that the legend
was true after all.
"Do not awaken what lies asleep here."
"On the night of the Red Moon,
the Red One will be roused from sleep
and return to the Black One."
"When they are reunited,
the world will turn into hell,
where only pain and darkness exist."
Now, the door to hell will open.
The door to hell.
I wasn't wrong.
I was not wrong.
Seonhwa,
it's time.
THE FIRST DAY
SAFELY STORE HAZARDOUS MATERIALS
TO ENSURE SAFETY
What was he before?
I heard he was a monk.
-A monk?
-Yes.
A Buddhist monk?
Really?
BUK-SAN, GWANGJU
VOW OF SILENCE: SILENT MEDITATION
Cheongseok.
Cheongseok, you've been silent
for about two years, right?
Isn't it difficult?
Of course.
It is harder to train yourself
not to do something that you can do.
WHEN CAN I STOP?
What do you think?
Until I tell you to stop, obviously.
Follow me.
Cheongseok.
Remember the story about the monster?
WHY DIDN'T THE BUDDHA
GET RID OF THE MONSTER?
Because they exist
but don't exist at the same time.
So the Buddha locked them up
far away from each other
so they could never meet again.
One in the Far West,
and the other one in the Far East.
He created a desert in the Far West
and locked it up there,
so no one could reach it.
In the Far East, he created
steep cliffs to lock up the other one.
Then the Buddha sent
two of his disciples to the East,
a virgin shaman and a nameless monk.
He told them to guard
the trails and the cliffs
so the two monsters
would never be reunited again.
But…
when the time comes,
the Red One in the West
will meet a helper.
On the night of the Red Moon,
the Red One will be freed.
It will then make its way back
through the seven stepping stones
for seven nights
and find its other half.
If they're reunited
on the eighth night…
We can't get rid of the monster,
but we can make sure
the two can't be reunited.
We can get rid of the stepping stones.
If we manage to get rid of
even just one of them,
those two can never be reunited.
Cheongseok.
I see dust piled up on the Urna.
Wipe it clean.
CHILGOK, GYEONGSANGBUK-DO
Damn it. It's tiny.
What's that?
THE SECOND DAY
-What does he do?
-Not sure. He said he's a professor.
-How did you meet him?
-Through a meditation group.
They say it's a meditation group,
but it was more like a cult.
My life's a mess,
so I went there
thinking it might be helpful.
And? Was it helpful?
Helpful?
Well, I guess so.
Got a health checkup for free.
-A health checkup?
-Nothing expensive.
Just a simple, quick blood test.
That's why you went there?
Of course not.
The organizer paid me
to keep attending the gatherings.
-They paid you?
-Yes.
FOUR SEASONS
Did you have a nightmare?
Cheongseok.
Good or bad, everything that's past
is nothing but a vain dream.
Do not let such dreams sway you.
The time has come.
Find Seonhwa.
SEONHWA
And tell him…
that the monster is here.
THE THIRD DAY
FOUR SEASONS - WELCOME
Hey, you got a photo of this shoeprint?
-I'll check now!
-What have you guys been doing? Jeez.
Hey, this tape should go
all the way around.
-Yes, sir.
-What the heck is this?
-Who called it in?
-The owner of the motel.
-Are there any witnesses?
-This place is very remote.
And it's a weekday, so no other guests.
-They're for your feet.
-What is this?
The owner of the motel was asleep
at the time of the incident.
Did you check that thing?
Yes. Around 11:45 p.m. last night,
the suspect… I mean, the victim.
-Which one is it?
-You're not making any sense.
Go check yourself.
There's a male body inside the bathroom.
The woman who was with him is gone.
Jeez…
The woman?
This man and a woman named Seo Gyeong-suk
checked in together.
The CCTV caught her leaving
right after the incident.
How did you get her name?
She left her stuff, including her wallet.
-Is there an APB out on her?
-Yes.
What is that?
That's the "suspect" I mentioned earlier.
From what I saw in the footage,
he was fine until he entered the room.
But as you can see now, he is…
SEONHWA
Shouldn't we let Seonhwa know?
-Do you know where he is?
-Yes.
-Don't tell him.
-But Bhante Hajeong is--
Don't bother.
Then what about his cremation rite?
No one cares about his death anyway,
so let's keep it simple.
Vow of silence?
For how long?
No one's making you
do it now, so you can stop.
DO YOU KNOW WHERE BHANTE SEONHWA IS?
I WILL BE BACK BEFORE THE CREMATION RITE
- CHEONGSEOK
Bhante Seonhwa.
Bhante, my foot.
He's not a monk?
-Can only a monk ascend us?
-How much longer do we have to wait?
Why doesn't he help us ascend?
You can help us ascend
even if you're not a monk, right?
Let us go! Why won't you let us go?
Help us ascend.
THE FOURTH DAY
DAEJEON STATION
EUNHAENG-DONG, DAEJEON
4-91
Seo Gyeong-suk was found dead
inside a restroom at a park.
Let's think simply.
These two checked in together.
And this man came in later.
It'd make sense
if these two were found dead.
But this guy was found dead.
She left the motel in one piece,
but didn't take her stuff
or call the police.
Then she was found dead today,
in a restroom.
Looking gross like the body at the motel.
What do you think happened?
What's your theory? You, tell us.
-Me?
-Yes, you.
Well…
It's a bizarre case,
and the bodies
that have been found look weird.
Right.
That said, my friend at the East Precinct…
He said…
-Nothing. Never mind, sir.
-Just finish your sentence.
-What did your friend say?
-I mean…
When he was trying
to catch a flasher recently,
he went to see a famous shaman--
A shaman?
He said she was good.
Are we trying to
catch ghosts here or what?
CHIEF
EVALUATION FOR PROMOTION
What are you going to do about Dong-jin?
You need to do something about him.
Yeah.
It's hard enough
with a perfectly healthy guy.
He limps and can't see well.
What will you do with him?
I got so frustrated yesterday
and told him to quit,
but he wanted to talk to you.
It's not your fault that he's like that.
It was an accident.
So stop making things
harder for the others
and let him go now, okay?
Why does he always ask us to pack this?
To give to his dog, I guess?
The police suspects suicide
and said an investigation is underway.
Coming up next,
a man in his sixties who was arrested
after assaulting his friend…
BHANTE SEONHWA?
BHANTE HAJEONG HAS PASSED AWAY.
HE TOLD ME TO TELL YOU
THAT THE MONSTER IS HERE.
I'M SORRY. I LOST THE THING
BHANTE HAJEONG LEFT BEHIND.
You must be the one
from the meditation group.
Is everything okay?
What happened to you?
VIRGIN SHAMAN
Your eyes are still filled with anger.
I figured I should see you,
so I came with him.
I told you over and over.
You must help souls ascend until you die.
That is your fate.
Look, Seonhwa.
I see that there are countless souls
on your back, waiting to ascend.
He is here.
He's already begun
jumping over the stepping stones.
Find her. The only stepping stone we know.
That woman, the virgin shaman.
You must find her before he gets there.
And…
kill her.
It is the fate of those
who must stand guard.
You will be my successor.
VIRGIN SHAMAN
45-12 SINPUNG-DONG, PALDAL-GU, SUWON
TO MR. PARK JIN-SU
THE FIFTH DAY
Bhante Seonhwa!
Thank you.
VOW OF SILENCE
Where are you going?
What is that?
Where are you headed?
Seo, a female in her forties and also
the suspect in the Daegu motel murder
was found dead in a park restroom.
The police are going through
the CCTV footage to retrace Seo's trail
in the hopes of finding witnesses.
The police suspect another accomplice may…
No, thanks.
May I go with you?
Bhante Hajeong told me to stay with you.
46-9 SINPUNG-DONG, PALDAL-GU
By the way, have we met before?
I feel comfortable
around you for some reason,
as if we've met before.
I'm not saying this
because you bought me nice shoes…
and food.
That's not why I'm saying it.
What I mean is…
You have sinned a lot.
Looking for someone?
Well…
The lady at the store said
you were looking for the shaman.
I heard she moved to Daegu a year ago.
Her address? That, I don't know.
But if you go there,
you'll die.
What do you mean?
NFS performed an autopsy
and even did a toxicology test,
but the cause of death is unknown.
Then how did they die?
-There are some things on the report--
-Just say it! Don't keep me hanging!
"The bodies decomposed overnight
and resulted in severe tissue damage…"
-What is this?
-What's this nonsense now?
What else?
It says that each victim
has a dent in their skull.
But they have to look into it more.
-Hey.
-Yes, we're at the scene.
Are you sure you called the NFS,
not a private
investigation agency somewhere?
Sir, I saw the bodies
again today, you know?
But it's really bizarre.
Remember the shaman
I told you about the other day?
-I went to see--
-You're at it again? I'm hanging up.
Have you put out an APB on the suspect?
-Yes, sir.
-Who's the victim?
Female, 28.
She was reported missing two days ago.
She went to see a friend
and never came back.
-Currently unemployed and…
-The dead don't work.
Pardon?
Jeez, it stinks.
-Pass me the gloves.
-Yes, sir.
WHERE ARE WE GOING?
WHO ARE YOU LOOKING FOR?
Jeez, you're so annoying.
See all the empty seats?
Why must you sit beside me?
-Just talk.
-Can I?
-Bhante Seonhwa, I thought it'd annoy--
-Don't call me that.
Pardon? Then what should I call you?
DAEGU BUS TERMINAL
I am choosing death to pay for what I did.
I know it's a lot to ask, but please,
look after my son, Jeong-hun,
who now has no one.
Once again, I'd like to apologize
to Mr. Park Jin-su and his family.
I am sorry.
-Kill him.
-Just kill him. Eye for an eye.
Kill him!
Just kill him!
You fool!
THE SIXTH DAY
Bhante Seonhwa.
I'm sorry.
You told me not to call you that.
What should I--
Did Bhante Hajeong
really tell you to stay with me?
-Enjoy.
-Thank you.
The motel, the restroom.
Are you a baby?
Do this yourself.
That's a double burger.
Listen up. See this area here?
We'll find every single shaman here today.
The public restroom
in the park is over there,
so you check from here
all the way to Gyobang-dong…
Here's your ice cream.
You little punk.
Find all of them
before sundown and meet me here.
-Is it good?
-Yes, it's so good.
I had ice cream
when Bhante Hajeong took me to…
GYOBANG GIL 91
GYOBANG 2-GIL 37 - 141
GEUMJEONGSA
WOMAN'S DEAD BODY FOUND
IN SEWER BY DAEGU TUNNEL
Due to the level of decomposition,
the police believe
that the incident took place a while ago…
VIRGIN SHAMAN
-Where are you, sir?
-At the scene. Why?
-Chief is looking for you.
-Okay. I'll be back in a bit.
Emergency near Jangan-dong.
We're on the way.
Excuse me.
May I see your ID?
-It's me.
-Yes, sir.
Can you look someone up?
Park Jin-su, 750121-1046411.
Patrol 7 here. Another body found
near Daegu High School.
Just a fine for causing
a disturbance in court. That's all.
Okay.
Just a second.
May I check your bag?
Damn it.
Is there any chance…
that we've met before?
DAEGU JUNGBU POLICE
Are you all right?
Did you check?
First off, the body found
near Daegu High School
was the delivery guy from the tunnel.
The body was in the same condition.
What the heck is happening here?
And here.
NAME: PARK JIN-SU
He was working
at a construction site in Daejeon
up until two days before the first case.
I spoke with the site manager.
In March 1999, he lost his wife
and his five-year-old daughter
in a car accident.
The driver was under
the influence of alcohol.
The driver got her sentence reduced…
And he caused
a disturbance in court. Okay.
"Assault"? What's this about?
I think this man
became a monk after the accident.
A Buddhist monk?
There's a small temple
in Gwangju, Jeolla Province.
Apparently, it's famous for exorcism--
-Another shaman?
-No, he's not a shaman.
I'd say he's an exorcist monk?
Stop writing a novel and get to the point.
The point is,
he beat someone up
to expel an evil spirit.
And got charged with assault.
They reached a settlement.
And this fraud charge?
The Jogye Order of Korean Buddhism
checked after helping him settle the case
and found out Park was never
ordained as a Buddhist monk.
He was never ordained?
Simply put, that's how
you obtain your ID as a Buddhist monk.
If he doesn't have that,
it means he's not a real monk.
Who is this prick?
DAEGU JUNGBU POLICE PRECINCT MAP
Damn it.
Anyway, this morning in Chilgok--
-Hey, Dong-jin.
-Yes?
Let's go.
Come with me.
Right.
Before I forget… Here.
-What is this?
-Clean underwear. Courtesy of my wife.
My goodness, she didn't have to do this.
And before I forget, here. Take this, too.
What's this?
I told you last time
about the virgin shaman.
-You idiot.
-No, don't!
It was very expensive.
It's not just any talisman.
See this?
My blood went into it
to make it even more effective.
-My own blood.
-Is this what you've been doing?
Come on. Just keep it on you at all times.
It'll ward off evil spirits
and help you catch the killer.
Then why do detectives even exist?
Shamans could catch the bad guys.
Hey, what did you say to me a while back?
You said we should try everything we can.
How are you feeling?
Better?
Well, my legs are much better now,
and my eyes, too.
The light has turned green.
You may cross now.
Ho-tae, you really
don't need to worry about me.
It was an accident.
It's not your fault that I got hurt.
You saved me when I jumped
in the water to kill myself.
And thanks to you, I became a cop.
Even if it was your fault
that I ended up like this,
I honestly wouldn't care.
So I'm just going to keep
working as a cop, okay?
MAP OF DAEGU
Did you see a virgin shaman in this area?
This is the park.
I went this way, and you this way.
Right there.
On the right.
It's here.
But I saw something strange
on my way back.
SUSEONG-GU
SEO-GU, JUNG-GU
What is this?
His face turned green when he heard
about the body on radio.
Pass me a pen.
The tunnel is here.
Daegu High School.
Gyobang-dong?
No new missing person reports
in the past few days.
This one's the only runaway.
But it's nothing new.
She's done this many times.
She usually comes home in a few weeks.
Her mother brought it about a year ago.
She made quite a scene and said
that her daughter would kill herself.
Kill herself?
Yes. She joined some kind of
suicide website and disappeared.
But from what I recall,
she returned home safely a few days later.
-Right?
-It wasn't a suicide website.
We found out later
it was a meditation group
created by people
who had attempted suicide.
You really saw that?
Are you sure?
What exactly did I see?
Listen carefully.
We're parting ways here.
We never met and you never even saw me.
If anyone asks, you don't know me.
Say you don't know me at all.
But I do know you.
I'll go with you…
-Go back to the temple.
-I don't want to.
I came all the way here.
I don't know what you're trying to do,
but I want to help.
I have to…
kill someone now.
If you stay with me,
you'll get in trouble.
You understand me?
The person you must kill…
-Is it the thing I saw?
-No, he can't be killed.
Then who…
If he's really been awakened,
she'll die at the hands
of that monster anyway.
-I don't understand.
-I don't have time to explain.
I must…
get rid of what he needs.
That's all I can do.
As for what happened in the past…
-Aren't you coming?
-No, you get going first.
All right.
Right, there was something
I wanted to tell you about.
What is it?
This morning, they found a dead body
in the mountains in Chilgok.
-They said that the body looked bizarre.
-How so?
Based on the description,
it sounded similar
to the victims in this case.
-Have you checked?
-I'm already on it.
The phone records,
e-mails, and bank records. You name it.
What do you say?
Am I competent enough
to keep working with you?
Just go home.
Come with me.
You have to run.
No time to explain.
Come on.
-What's up?
-It's about the body found in Chilgok.
-I think it's connected to this case.
-Go on.
Name, Kim Jun-cheol. An anthropologist.
Shunned by academia after
the relic forgery case 13 years ago.
From 2016 onwards,
he ran a Buddhist meditation website
called BMS up until a year ago,
and they were all members of this site.
-"They"? Who?
-The weird-looking corpses.
On the website, there are a few photos
from their offline gathering in Daegu.
Except for two people,
everyone in the photos
was found dead in that grotesque state.
But the thing is,
do you know who those two people are?
-Who are they?
-I was so surprised when I saw this photo.
The runaway girl
we heard about at the substation earlier.
The other is the shaman
who made that talisman I gave you.
-They're the two people.
-Where are you now?
I'm at the office.
Give me the shaman's address.
Gyobang-dong, right? Meet me there.
You bastard.
I won't lose you twice.
She already ran away.
That sly bitch.
OM
-It's over now.
-He'll die soon.
-He's done for.
-Useless prick.
He's useless now.
Help us ascend? As if.
-What was the point of waiting?
-Let's go.
Why isn't he picking up?
That's weird.
I'm pretty sure I came this way last time.
What's going on? Is that the runaway girl?
-What's wrong?
-Over there.
Don't move.
Drop your weapon. I said, drop it!
Call from an alleyway,
Gyobang 3-dong redevelopment area.
This is Patrol 8.
We're near that area now.
We'll head over.
This is not where you'll die.
Go to Buk-San.
You two over there.
What are you doing here?
Hey, get him!
This is Patrol 8.
Send backup to Gyobang 3-dong.
Here.
Two for Gwangju, please.
THE SEVENTH DAY
Bhante Hajeong?
GO TO BUK-SAN AND
YOU'LL FIND WHAT YOU ARE LOOKING FOR.
-To Gwangju, please.
-Go to the terminal to get there.
-Then can you drop me off at the terminal?
-Sure.
Taxi!
Taxi.
-Gwangju, please.
-Last one just left.
Next one is in three hours.
JUNE 13, 2:01 A.M.
GO TO BUK-SAN AND
YOU'LL FIND WHAT YOU ARE LOOKING FOR.
The last stepping stone I was looking for.
That woman, the virgin shaman.
But why…
Are you afraid?
Right. Everyone runs away
when faced with fear.
Look.
They all left, thinking you'd die soon.
That means…
he is already on the last stepping stone.
Now, you are the only one that's left.
Like I said,
whether you run away alive or dead,
your fate as the guard will not end.
You became the guard because I died.
So if you run away or die,
someone else
will take over as your successor.
Bhante Seonhwa!
Now, the choice is yours.
Mister.
I'm sorry.
But why did my mom die?
JUNE 13, 4:54 A.M.
To Gwangju, please.
That makes no sense!
Why would he do such a thing
when he has a wife and a kid?
Let's just wait.
Maybe someone stole
Dong-jin's car and gun.
Move.
PLATE NUMBER: 23S 7657
To Buk-San, please.
Maybe that's why the head monk said
we should keep it simple…
I'll call you later.
Hey!
What are you doing?
What…
What will you do now?
Both he and the sarira casket
are on their way back here now.
Have you found any witnesses yet?
They heard some people fight
and called the police,
but didn't really see anything.
I don't care.
Just find evidence
that it wasn't Dong-jin.
Yes, sir.
Are you getting tired?
I'm Cheongseok.
It means green grass.
My name is…
Ae-ran.
Were you here alone?
When I first met her,
I didn't know she was a ghost.
No one there knew
that she was there with us.
That night, she followed me.
Then all night, she told me what happened.
An abused girl.
She believed that life was a curse.
She wished that all of it
would just end quickly.
Then one day,
a man showed up like her savior.
Let's go.
But happiness is always short-lived.
And always…
No! That is not true!
No. I am not wrong.
This is what it says here.
"The one who
bewitches the virgin, the red-eyed maid."
I need this maid
as a sacrificial offering.
Do you think I'm crazy?
Even if no one believes me,
you believe Daddy, right?
The virgin shaman who guards
the path will be the last stepping stone.
A sacrificial offering.
Someone who can bewitch the virgin
and stall her.
Even if no one believes me,
you believe Daddy, right?
If it's something
that someone you love said,
you always want to believe it,
no matter how foolish it is.
Is that why life is a tragedy?
-Why is this…
-Why is it there?
Two for Gwangju, please.
To Buk-San, please.
That detective?
He was here a few days ago.
I made him a talisman with his blood.
But the thing is…
he didn't seem to know
he was already dead.
That meditation group…
Everyone there had no idea either.
That they were all
destined to die years ago.
They were alive because they couldn't die.
They were hanging by a thread.
I don't know
how that professor found them.
He brought them all together.
Then he used them
as sacrificial offerings,
as the stepping stones.
The Red One
will follow the smell of their blood
and step on the stepping stones one by one
to go to the Black One.
Then…
What are you doing?
That detective
has the same natal chart as mine.
So he became the stepping stone for me.
That girl kept me here so I couldn't run.
Ae-ran told me in secret
that I'd be able to live if I did that.
Even so, it's not my fault
that cop ended up like that. It's…
the person who
pulled him out of the water…
It was you.
Because of you, he couldn't die
when he was supposed to die.
Then it's your fault, not mine.
Figure it out yourself, then.
Why come to me?
Go to Buk-San.
Those who are chained
all went to the one holding the chain.
They're all his now.
Leave.
I have nowhere to go.
Fine.
But…
we will now set up a trap to catch him.
I'll use myself as bait.
No matter what he does
once he's in the trap,
do only what I say.
I'll turn your clothes into your talisman,
so do not take them off.
Go to Buk-San,
and you'll find what you're looking for.
Am I competent enough
to keep working with you?
So I'm just going to keep
working as a cop, okay?
DAEGU
What will happen
when the sarira casket is open?
The Black One and the Red One
will be reunited again.
What are the Black One and the Red One?
Anxiety is what you feel
when you live in anguish
while waiting for the unknown.
The eyes of an anxious person
look dark, devoid of any spark.
Agony is what you feel when you're sad
because you can't get over
something that happened in the past.
The eyes of a person suffering
from such agony burn with anger.
Therefore, anxiety is black,
and agony is red.
Such formless black and red things
make us suffer so much.
What do you think will happen
if they're reunited and become one?
A world where both the living and the dead
suffer in despair and anger,
trapped in anxiety and agony.
A world of endless night.
That is…
That is hell.
THE EIGHTH DAY
We have nowhere to run.
I'll be his last target.
When he crawls into my body
once he's caught inside the trap…
Slay me without hesitation.
You are foolish.
My final destination is the body
of the one who can open the sarira casket.
Only the one who guards
the sarira casket can open it.
The day you became a monk in Buk-San,
you became Hajeong's successor,
the only person
who can open the sarira casket.
However,
because you left
this mountain and ran away,
you can no longer open
the sarira casket. Hajeong's successor is…
OM
Which means,
no one needs you anymore.
You're useless.
So…
just die.
Ae-ran, find him.
Ae-ran!
OM
Dong-jin!
Park Dong-jin!
Jeong-hun! Run!
Run!
You asshole.
What's wrong with you?
What were you thinking?
-Ho-tae, run. Get out of here.
-Dong-jin.
Stay away!
Run!
Bhante Seonhwa, help me!
Bhante Seonhwa!
Dong-jin.
You're so annoying.
Ho-tae.
Let's…
go home.
Just come to me.
This kid… Don't hurt him.
I guess you forgot.
This boy is the son
of the woman you used to hate.
What do you think you'll mean to this boy?
Let's go.
The light is…
too…
far.
My mom killed your entire family.
I'm sure you wanted her
to suffer the same.
It's not too late yet.
This is your last chance.
Your last chance to put an end
to everything once and for all.
Do not give up
like the night you left the temple.
Strangle me with all your strength.
Then those nights that felt like hell
will all disappear.
You gave up your last chance
to put an end to your pent-up
anguish and resentment.
You are still unbelievably foolish.
OM
Jeong-hun!
I'm sorry…
for everything.
When the darkness deepens,
the light becomes even brighter.
The deeper the agony,
the greater the nirvana will be.
What is life?
Life is like a short-lived flower.
All your dreams
and fantasies are like sea foam,
like shadows, dewdrops, and lightning.
It is truly futile.
But even if it's a futile, fleeting moment
in our predetermined fate,
everything is meaningful in its own way.
Seonhwa.
Now that you've found that meaning,
it's time for you to wake up
from your sad dream.
Subtitle translation by: Eui Soo Seo